bobevans.com 2010-12-03

# Bob Evans, Discover Farm-Fresh Goodness | Privacy Policy

BobEvans.com knows that you care about how your information is used and shared, which is why we have posted this Privacy Policy. Simply stated, the following Privacy Policy statement explains what information we collect from you, how we use that information and what choices you have with respect to that information.

This Privacy Policy statement applies only to the information collected online in the general portions of the BobEvans.com Web site and any affiliated microsites that reference this policy. If you would like to review the privacy policy for the Kid Times portion of our Web site ([kids.bobevans.com](https://kids.bobevans.com/)) please [click here](https://kids.bobevans.com/).

### TABLE OF CONTENTS

  * What Type of Information do we Collect?
  * How do we use Personal Information Collected Online?
  * What Information do we Share with or Disclose to Third Parties?
  * Public Forums
  * Update your Personal Information
  * Opting Out of Bob Evans Email
  * Cookies
  * Privacy of Children on our Web Site
  * Links to other Web Sites and Services
  * Updates to this Privacy Policy
  * Security
  * Questions or Concerns

### What Type of Information do we Collect?

We gather information through two means – navigational information gathered when you visit our Web site and personal information that you provide to us. Generally, the information we collect online helps us respond to your requests, deliver requested services to or for you, and personalize and continually improve your experience at BobEvans.com.

   1\. Navigational Information:  
      When visiting our Web site, BobEvans.com gathers navigational information about where visitors go on our Web site and how our site is working. This information allows us to see which areas of our Web site are most visited and the efficiencies of our site for our visitors. We can thus improve the quality of our visitors’ experience by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (for example, domain type, browser version, service provider, and IP address) may be collected, which provides additional information regarding a visitor’s use of our Web site. BobEvans.com uses this information on an aggregate basis to evaluate the effectiveness of our Web site, to analyze trends and to administer the Web site.

   2\. Personal Information:  
      BobEvans.com may ask you to provide personal information when you establish or update an e-mail account, sign up to receive e-mails or other marketing materials from BobEvans.com, make a gift card purchase, submit a video or a photograph, submit a corporate giving request, send a recipe to a friend, submit a real estate inquiry, request investor information or create a stockholder account, contact us, participate in a contest, complete an employment application, or utilize any other feature where BobEvans.com may need to reply to your activity. 

      The personal information we collect may include name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, recipient’s name and address, order information, credit card information, and any other information you choose to provide. If you submit an employment application the information you submit may also include a resume, the type of position you are seeking, your educational background, work experience, salary requirements, and any other information you choose to provide.

Back to Top

### How do we use Personal Information Collected Online?

BobEvans.com may use the personal information we collect from you for the following purposes:

  * to send information about our products, events, promotions, contests, and recipes;
  * to respond to your inquiries;
  * to develop our products, services, Web site and affiliated microsites;
  * to tailor your experience on our Web site or affiliated microsites and the information sent through e-mail to your interests;
  * to deliver gift cards that you have ordered, fulfill requests that you have submitted, and respond to a request for a corporate gift;
  * to fulfill your request to send recipes or other information to another party. Recipient information will only be used for purposes of fulfilling your request. BobEvans.com does not retain or review any personally identifiable information that you may provide when submitting such a request, but in the event of delivery failure we may contact you or the recipient;
  * to post photographs and videos you submit to the Web site;
  * to provide you with the location information you request. BobEvans.com also uses the information provided through locator services on an aggregate basis to analyze trends and help us determine what store or product information is most frequently accessed by our visitors; and
  * to evaluate your employment application. If you elect to complete an employment application through our Web site, any information that you provide to us is only used to enable Bob Evans Farms, Inc. to consider your interest in employment with Bob Evans and, if hired, for employment and business-related purposes.

Back to Top

### What Information do we Share with or Disclose to Third Parties

We use third parties to help us provide services to you, such as fulfilling online gift card orders, providing electronic online investor information, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, providing location information, and administering e-mails or contests that may occasionally be offered at this Web site or affiliated microsites. If personally identifiable information (i.e., name, address, e-mail address, telephone number) is provided by us or by you directly to any of these third parties, we will require that such information be maintained by them in confidence. Information you provide directly to our third party service provider for electronic online investor information may be shared with us. In the future we may share information with companies in whom we own an interest, for example, Mimi’s Café and Owens Foods.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any preexisting Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). If Bob Evans Farms, Inc., or substantially all of its assets were ever acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. Otherwise, BobEvans.com does not sell, rent, or trade the information that you provide to us at this Web site.

You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our Web site, the site or the public.

Back to Top

### Public Forums

BobEvans.com or microsites operated or provided by Bob Evans Farms, Inc. or any of its affiliates may make forums available to its users at various times or the ability for users of the website or microsite to upload photographs or videos. Please remember that, unless otherwise stated, any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas (including uploading photos and videos into these areas that contain your image). Bob Evans has specific terms in its Site Use Terms and Conditions and may also have specific Requirements and Terms for these features and you must agree to comply with all of these terms and requirements prior to your initial use of and uploading to these public forums.

Back to Top

### Update your Personal Information

We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up to date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your BE-mail account by logging in to your account using your password via <http://www.bobevans.com/bemail>.

Back to Top

### Opting Out of Bob Evans Email

If you previously signed up to receive Bob Evans marketing materials via e-mail but would now like to be removed from the Bob Evans e-mail marketing list, you can use the “unsubscribe” feature on our e-mails, send your request to [customer_support@bobevans.com](mailto:customer_support@bobevans.com), or change your e-mail account preferences by visiting http://www.bobevans.com/bemail. Please be aware, even if you do not “opt-in” to, or subsequently ask to be removed from, the BobEvans.com e-mail marketing list, you may still receive e-mail confirmations for any gift card purchases made on our Web site. In addition, please be aware that if you sign up to receive Bob Evans Kid Times e-mails on the Kid Times portion of our Web site ([kids.bobevans.com](https://kids.bobevans.com/)), asking to be removed from the BobEvans.com e-mail marketing list will not remove you from the Bob Evans Kid Times e-mail list. For information on how to remove yourself from that list, please visit the privacy policy for the Kid Times portion of our Web site by [clicking here](https://kids.bobevans.com/).

Back to Top

### Cookies

BobEvans.com does not currently, but may in the future, use a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are typically stored on your computer’s hard drive and allow a Web site to be more responsive to your needs, while delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. Please also be aware that some of the third party service providers that we use on this Web site to help us provide services to you (for example, the store locator) may use cookies.

Most browsers allow the user to limit the use of cookies. However, if you block the use of cookies from our Web site you may not be able to utilize certain features of our Web site.

Back to Top

### Privacy of Children on our Web Site

To ensure compliance with federal law, the general portions of BobEvans.com and any microsites operated or provided by Bob Evans Farms, Inc. or any of its affiliates that reference this policy do not knowingly collect or maintain information provided by children under the age of 13. If you would like to review the privacy policy for the Kid Times portion of our Web site ([kids.bobevans.com](https://kids.bobevans.com/)), please [click here](https://kids.bobevans.com/).

Back to Top

### Links to other Web Sites and Services

For your convenience, our Web site may contain links to other Web sites. BobEvans.com is not responsible for the privacy practices, advertising, products, or the content of such Web sites. We urge you to review the privacy policies on each link to ensure that you are comfortable with their privacy policies and practices. In addition, none of the linked Web sites that appear on the BobEvans.com Web site should be deemed to imply that BobEvans.com endorses or has any affiliation with such Web sites.

Back to Top

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

As we continue to offer you new and different types of content and services, BobEvans.com may modify our information collection and use practices. Should there be a material change to our information practices, it will be applied only to information collected on a going forward basis, and we will update this Privacy Policy statement. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our Web site for this and other important announcements from BobEvans.com.

Back to Top

### Security

We accept online applications, resumes and gift card orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. For example, 3.0 versions or higher of Netscape Navigator and versions of 3.02 or higher of Internet Explorer. This means you’ll be unable to inadvertently submit an online application or resume or place an order through an unsecured connection. Please be aware, however, that any information sent through the Contact Us feature on this Web site is not sent through an encrypted or secured connection.

As an additional security measure, it is our policy to never send credit card information via e-mail. In addition, BobEvans.com limits the number of employees that have access to the databases that contain personal information, and all BobEvans.com employees are advised of the importance of confidentiality.

Back to Top

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at [customer_support@bobevans.com](mailto:customer_support@bobevans.com).

3776 S. High Street  
Columbus, Ohio 43207  
(800) 272-7675

Policy Effective: January 8, 2009.

Back to Top
